# Moses Chukwunekwu

### **Frontend Engineer**

Frontend Engineer with industry experience building web applications. Specialties in **JavaScript/Typescript**, **HTML/CSS** and **React JS/Redux**. Adept at writing and styling frontend components that meet the requirements of mocks and fulfill user stories.

Lagos, Nigeria (234) 90 6988 5063 dantereus1@gmail.com https://github.com/moses-py/

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Garmatsch Software, Berlin, Germany— Frontend Engineer

December 2020 - October 2022

- Frontend architecture & development (TypeScript, React JS, Storybook, CSSin-JS, GraphQL)
- Created and developed design mock for company homepage
- Collaborated with a team of 6 developers to develop an internal reusable component library
- Assisted in conducting code reviews and peer-to-peer programming

### McMakler GmbH, Berlin, Germany— Frontend Engineer

June 2021- December 2021

- Developed a map-data visualization program for Real estate data search with server side rendering.
- Implemented MapBox GL with customizations and data visualization in grids and lists

# Frontend developer & Software Intern Trainer at Kodegenic Ltd, Uyo, Nigeria— Software Engineer

November 2018 - December 2020

- Communicated effectively with company managers to understand the training and development needs of Interns
- Collaborated with Interns and Junior developers to develop a Savings and Deposit platform

# develop a Savings and Deposit platform LANG

### **EDUCATION**

### Brigham Young University, Idaho, USA—B.Sc

January 2020 - Present

Computer Science & Applied Technology

#### **SKILLS**

Frontend: TypeScript. JavaScript, ReactJS, Redux, GraphQL, NextJS, CSS3, CSS-in-JS, HTML5, CSSFrameworks (MaterialUI, SCSS), Apollo Client

**Backend**: NodeJS, ExpressJS, RESTful APIs, Mongoose, Apollo GraphQL, MongoDB

**Tools**: Git, Github, Firebase, VS Code, npm, yarn, Postman, JEST, React-testing-library

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

The Completer 2020 Web development Bootcamp by Dr Angela Yu

React - The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux) by Maximilian Schwarxmüller

**React Certification** by HackerRank: <a href="https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/eeae9ff543b8">https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/eeae9ff543b8</a>

### **LANGUAGES**

English